export const hangulCharacters = {
    consonants: [
        {
            question: 'ㄱ',
            answer: ['g', 'k']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㄲ',
            answer: ['gg', 'kk']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㄴ',
            answer: ['n']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㄷ',
            answer: ['d', 't']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㄸ',
            answer: ['tt']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㄹ',
            answer: ['r', 'l']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅁ', 
            answer: ['m']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅂ',
            answer: ['b', 'p']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅃ',
            answer: ['bb', 'pp']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅅ',
            answer: ['s', 't']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅆ',
            answer: ['ss']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅇ',
            answer: ['ng']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅈ',
            answer: ['j']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅉ',
            answer: ['jj']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅊ',
            answer: ['ch']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅋ',
            answer: ['k']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅌ',
            answer: ['t']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅍ',
            answer: ['p']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅎ',
            answer: ['h']
        },
    ],
    vowels: [
        {
            question: 'ㅏ',
            answer: ['a']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅐ',
            answer: ['ae']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅑ',
            answer: ['ya']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅒ',
            answer: ['yae']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅓ',
            answer: ['eo']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅔ',
            answer: ['e']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅕ',
            answer: ['yeo']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅖ',
            answer: ['ye']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅗ',
            answer: ['o']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅘ',
            answer: ['wa']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅙ',
            answer: ['wae']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅚ',
            answer: ['oe']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅛ',
            answer: ['yo']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅜ',
            answer: ['u']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅝ',
            answer: ['wo']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅞ',
            answer: ['we']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅟ',
            answer: ['wi']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅠ',
            answer: ['yu']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅡ',
            answer: ['eu']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅢ',
            answer: ['ui']
        },
        {
            question: 'ㅣ',
            answer: ['i']
        }
    ],
};

export const scoreInitialState = {
    correct: 0,
    total: 0
};